<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Daily Journey</string>
    <string name="expand_more_less">See more or less about this Scripture verses</string>
    <string name="day1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="verse1">Hebrews 10:24–25</string>
    <string name="text1">And let us consider how we may spur one another on toward love and good deeds, not giving up meeting together, as some are in the habit of doing, but encouraging one another—and all the more as you see the Day approaching.</string>
    <string name="day2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="verse2">Psalm 95:4–5</string>
    <string name="text2"> In his hand are the depths of the earth, and the mountain peaks belong to him. The sea is his, for he made it, and his hands formed the dry land.</string>
    <string name="day3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="verse3">Matthew 6:26–28</string>
    <string name="text3">Look at the birds of the air; they do not sow or reap or store away in barns, and yet your heavenly Father feeds them. Are you not much more valuable than they? Can any one of you by worrying add a single hour to your life? And why do you worry about clothes? See how the flowers of the field grow. They do not labor or spin.</string>
    <string name="day4">Day 4</string>
    <string name="verse4">Psalm 127:3</string>
    <string name="text4">Children are a heritage from the Lord, offspring a reward from him.</string>
    <string name="day5">Day 5</string>
    <string name="verse5">Psalm 82:3</string>
    <string name="text5">Defend the weak and the fatherless; uphold the cause of the poor and the oppressed.</string>
    <string name="day6">Day 6</string>
    <string name="verse6">John 14:27</string>
    <string name="text6">Peace I leave with you; my peace I give you. I do not give to you as the world gives. Do not let your hearts be troubled and do not be afraid.</string>
    <string name="day7">Day 7</string>
    <string name="verse7">Matthew 5:16</string>
    <string name="text7">Let your light shine before men in such a way that they may see your good works, and glorify your Father who is in heaven.</string>
    <string name="day8">Day 8</string>
    <string name="verse8">1 Corinthians 6:9–10</string>
    <string name="text8">Or do you not know that wrongdoers will not inherit the kingdom of God? Do not be deceived: Neither the sexually immoral nor idolaters nor adulterers nor men who have sex with men nor thieves nor the greedy nor drunkards nor slanderers nor swindlers will inherit the kingdom of God.</string>
    <string name="day9">Day 9</string>
    <string name="verse9">Ephesians 2:8–10</string>
    <string name="text9">For it is by grace you have been saved, through faith - and this is not from yourselves, it is the gift of God - not by works, so that no one can boast. For we are God’s handiwork, created in Christ Jesus to do good works, which God prepared in advance for us to do.</string>
    <string name="day10">Day 10</string>
    <string name="verse10">Romans 12:10</string>
    <string name="text10">Be devoted to one another in love. Honor one another above yourselves.</string>
    <string name="day11">Day 11</string>
    <string name="verse11">Lamentations 3:22–23</string>
    <string name="text11">The steadfast love of the Lord never ceases; his mercies never come to an end; they are new every morning; great is your faithfulness.</string>
    <string name="day12">Day 12</string>
    <string name="verse12">Philippians 4:6</string>
    <string name="text12">Do not be anxious about anything, but in everything by prayer and supplication with thanksgiving let your requests be made known to God.</string>
    <string name="day13">Day 13</string>
    <string name="verse13">Colossians 3:12</string>
    <string name="text13">Therefore, as God’s chosen people, holy and dearly loved, clothe yourselves with compassion, kindness, humility, gentleness and patience.</string>
    <string name="day14">Day 14</string>
    <string name="verse14">1 John 4:9</string>
    <string name="text14">This is how God showed his love among us: He sent his one and only Son into the world that we might live through him.</string>
    <string name="day15">Day 15</string>
    <string name="verse15">Jeremiah 29:11</string>
    <string name="text15">"For I know the plans I have for you," declares the Lord, "plans to prosper you and not to harm you, plans to give you hope and a future."</string>
    <string name="day16">Day 16</string>
    <string name="verse16">Proverbs 3:5–6</string>
    <string name="text16">Trust in the Lord with all your heart, and do not lean on your own understanding. In all your ways acknowledge him, and he will make straight your paths.</string>
    <string name="day17">Day 17</string>
    <string name="verse17">Psalm 23:1–3</string>
    <string name="text17">The LORD is my shepherd; I shall not want. He makes me lie down in green pastures; He leads me beside quiet waters. He restores my soul; He guides me in the paths of righteousness for the sake of His name.</string>
    <string name="day18">Day 18</string>
    <string name="verse18">Matthew 11:28–30</string>
    <string name="text18">“Come to me, all you who are weary and burdened, and I will give you rest. Take my yoke upon you and learn from me, for I am gentle and humble in heart, and you will find rest for your souls. For my yoke is easy and my burden is light.”</string>
    <string name="day19">Day 19</string>
    <string name="verse19">Proverbs 14:31</string>
    <string name="text19">Whoever oppresses a poor man insults his Maker, but he who is generous to the needy honors him.</string>
    <string name="day20">Day 20</string>
    <string name="verse20">Isaiah 9:6</string>
    <string name="text20">For to us a child is born, to us a son is given, and the government will be on his shoulders. And he will be called Wonderful Counselor, Mighty God, Everlasting Father, Prince of Peace.</string>
    <string name="day21">Day 21</string>
    <string name="verse21">Romans 12:2</string>
    <string name="text21">Do not conform to the pattern of this world, but be transformed by the renewing of your mind. Then you will be able to test and approve what God’s will is - his good, pleasing and perfect will.</string>
    <string name="day22">Day 22</string>
    <string name="verse22">2 Timothy 3:16</string>
    <string name="text22">All scripture is given by inspiration of God, and is profitable for doctrine, for reproof, for correction, for instruction in righteousness.</string>
    <string name="day23">Day 23</string>
    <string name="verse23">Galatians 5:22–23</string>
    <string name="text23">But the fruit of the Spirit is love, joy, peace, forbearance, kindness, goodness, faithfulness,  gentleness and self-control. Against such things there is no law.</string>
    <string name="day24">Day 24</string>
    <string name="verse24">1 John 1:6</string>
    <string name="text24">If we claim to have fellowship with him and yet walk in the darkness, we lie and do not live out the truth. </string>
    <string name="day25">Day 25</string>
    <string name="verse25">Ezekiel 36:25–26</string>
    <string name="text25">I will sprinkle clean water on you, and you will be clean; I will cleanse you from all your impurities and from all your idols. I will give you a new heart and put a new spirit in you; I will remove from you your heart of stone and give you a heart of flesh.</string>
    <string name="day26">Day 26</string>
    <string name="verse26">Psalm 119:105</string>
    <string name="text26">Your word is a lamp for my feet, a light on my path.</string>
    <string name="day27">Day 27</string>
    <string name="verse27">Colossians 3:17</string>
    <string name="text27">And whatever you do, whether in word or deed, do it all in the name of the Lord Jesus, giving thanks to God the Father through him.</string>
    <string name="day28">Day 28</string>
    <string name="verse28">Matthew 6:3-4</string>
    <string name="text28">But when you give to the needy, do not let your left hand know what your right hand is doing, so that your giving may be in secret. Then your Father, who sees what is done in secret, will reward you.</string>
    <string name="day29">Day 29</string>
    <string name="verse29">Proverbs 1:7</string>
    <string name="text29">The fear of the Lord is the beginning of knowledge, but fools despise wisdom and instruction.</string>
    <string name="day30">Day 30</string>
    <string name="verse30">Matthew 7:13-14</string>
    <string name="text30">Enter through the narrow gate. For wide is the gate and broad is the road that leads to destruction, and many enter through it. But small is the gate and narrow the road that leads to life, and only a few find it.</string>
</resources>